Guide to the Richard Maass Collection of Westchester and New York State 1645-1995, (Bulk: 1645-1910) MSS 055
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: New York State
  - Subseries A: Letters and Documents
    - creator: Tory document. place: Hartford, Jul 29, 1776; 055-001-a-0095; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 35)
      Five NY Tories ask to be released from custody. Signed by them, including Stephen De Lancey.
    - creator: Hampton, Mrs. A. place: Three miles from New York, Aug 4, 1776; 055-001-a-0096; 2.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 36)
      physical description: folded half sheet; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 20cm x 33cm
      To my dear child [her daughter]. Description of the arrival of the British in New York City.
    - creator: Schuyler, Philip John, 1733-1804. place: German Flats, Aug 13, 1776; 055-001-a-0099; 3.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 37)
      Memorandum of Mr. McDonald's information (About desertion and treason among his troops).
    - creator: Biddle, Clement place: Perth Amboy, Sep 18, 1776; 055-001-a-0103; 4.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 38)
      physical description: single half sheet (broken in two pieces); a.l.s.
      dimensions: 23cm x 38cm
      To Dear brother. Biddle describes the evacuation of New York.
    - creator: Axtell, William. place: Brooklyn, Oct 1776; 055-001-a-0108; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 39)
      dimensions: 19cm x 16cm
      Note witnessing an oath of allegiance to the Crown made by Ewert Bancker.
    - creator: Magaw, Robert. place: Harlem Heights, Oct 18, 1776; 055-001-a-0109; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 40)
      To The Honorable Council of Safety for the State of Pennsylvania.
    - creator: Sands, Comfort. place: [Albany], Nov 6, 1776; 055-001-a-0110; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 41)
      dimensions: 20 cm x 15cm
      Notice of payment to Thomas Pettit for services to the New York Convention.
    - creator: Jay, John, 1745-1829. place: New York, Apr 29, 1777; 055-001-a-0111; 5.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 42)
      physical description: folded full sheet, single half sheet (20cm x 33cm); a.l.s.
      dimensions: 40cm x 33cm
      Draft of letter to Livingston and Morris regarding the establishment of the New York judicial system.
    - creator: Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert Du Motier, marquis de, 1757-1834 place: s.l., Mar 19, 1778; 055-001-a-0117; 3.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 43)
      dimensions: 24cm x 37cm
      To Governor George Clinton.
    - creator: Office of Ordinance place: New York, Aug 11, 1778; 055-001-a-0121; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 44)
      physical description: folded full sheet (ProPatria watermark); a. d.s.
      British ship ordinance.
    - creator: Pass for Hempstead Ferry place: New York, Sep 10, 1778; 055-001-a-0122; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 45)
      dimensions: 21cm x 17cm
    - creator: Wayne, Anthony, 1745-1796. place: Fredericksburg, Nov 22, 1778; 055-001-a-0123; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 46)
      To Col. Bland.
    - creator: Jay, John, 1745-1829. place: s.l., Feb 4, 1779; 055-001-a-0124; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 47)
      physical description: fragment of half sheet; a.l.s. [draft]
      dimensions: 15cm x 19cm
      To George Clinton.
    - creator: Miralles, Juan de. place: Philadelphia, Jul 24, 1779; 055-001-a-0125; 3.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 48)
      dimensions: 42cm x 30cm
      To Joseph de Galvez, About Stony Point.
    - creator: Miralles, Juan de. place: Philadelphia, Jul 27, 1779; 055-001-a-0129; 10.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 49)
      physical description: Three full sheets quired and stitched; a. d.s.
      Descriptions of the attack on Stony Point.
    - creator: Ten Broeck, Abraham. place: Albany, Dec 11, 1779; 055-001-a-0140; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 50)
      physical description: folded full sheet, wax seal fragments (ProPatria); a.l.s.
      To Stephen Van Rensselaer.
    - creator: Livingston, John R. place: Boston, Feb 11, 1780; 055-001-a-0141; 2.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 51)
      physical description: folded full sheet, multiple repairs, wax seal fragments; a.l.s.
      To William Duer.
    - creator: Eliot, Andrew. place: New York, Jun 13, 1780; 055-001-a-0144; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 52)
      physical description: half sheet; d.s.
      dimensions: 31cm x 18cm
      Pass for a sloop to Huntington.
    - creator: Holland, Stephen. place: New York, 1781; 055-001-a-0145; 2.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 53)
      physical description: half sheet; a. l. [draft]
      dimensions: 39cm x 24cm
      To General John Sullivan. Draft of letter in Clements Library. Holland tests Sullivan's attachment to the Revolution.
    - creator: Morris, Lewis, 1671-1746. place: Philadelphia, Apr 1, 1781; 055-001-a-0148; 3.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 54)
      physical description: half sheet; a.l.s.
      To his son.
    - creator: De Lancey, Oliver, 1718-1785. place: [New York], Jun 22, 1781; 055-001-a-0152; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 55)
      dimensions: 19cm x 24cm
    - creator: Marshall, Christopher. place: Albany, Oct 24, 1781; 055-001-a-0153; 2.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 56)
      dimensions: 22cm x 35cm
      To Major General Lord Sterling
    - creator: Morris, Gouverneur, 1752-1816. place: Philadelphia, Jun 18, 1784; 055-001-a-0156; 4.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 57)
      physical description: folded full sheet (Britannia); a. l. s (retained copy)
      dimensions: 41cm x 34cm
      To Peter Van Schaack
    - creator: Clinton, George, 1739-1812. place: New York, May 5, 1789; 055-001-a-0161; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 58)
      physical description: folded half sheet (Horn in crowned shield); l. s.
      dimensions: 24cm x 39cm
      To The Governor of Massachusetts, sends the New York legislature's amendments for the Constitution.
    - creator: Huntington, Samuel, 1731-1796. place: Norwich (Connecticut), Aug 12, 1789; 055-001-a-0162; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 59)
      dimensions: 21cm x 31cm
      To George Clinton, regarding New York's proposals for amending the Constitution.
    - creator: Deed of sale of Tory lands place: [New York], Apr 16, 1792; 055-001-a-0163; 2.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 60)
      physical description: two sheets wove paper, fastened with wax at corner; d.s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 26cm, 20cm x 32cm
      1832 copy of original documents relating to the sale of property at Corlaers Hook to Henry Roome in 1792.
    - creator: Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795. place: [New York], Aug 8, 1792; 055-001-a-0166; 6.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 61)
      physical description: two folded half sheets; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 23cm x 37cm
      To 'Your Royal Highness.'
    - creator: Stuart, John, Sir, 1759-1815. place: Oreque, France, May 17, 1793; 055-001-a-0173; 8.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 62)
      physical description: two folded half sheets, pasted flap on crease of each sheet; a.l.s.
      To unknown correspondent.
    - creator: Fraunces, Samuel place: [Philadelphia], Feb 17, 1794; 055-001-a-0182; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 63)
      physical description: fragment of sheet mounted on cardboard.; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 17cm x 10cm
      Receipt for purchase of 'sundries' for the President's household.
    - creator: Ritt, Frederick place: [Philadelphia], Jan 4, 1796; 055-001-a-0183; 1.0 pages (Box 2, Folder 64)
      physical description: fragment of sheet mounted on cardboard.; a. n. s.
      dimensions: 16cm x 9cm
  - Subseries B: James Alexander Collection
    Series I: Subseries B is the James Alexander Collection. It contains eight letters to and from Alexander (1691-1756) and his wife, Mary, housed in one small legal box. Alexander was surveyor-general of New York and New Jersey, an attorney, and a contributor to the New York Weekly Journal. In 1735 he was disbarred because he served as counsel for Journal editor Peter Zenger in the famous freedom-of-the-press case. Alexander also was a co-founder of the American Philosophical Society. The James Alexander Collection was purchased as a group by Mr. Maass.
    - creator: Barclay to J. Alexander. place: London, Feb 15, 1732; 055-001-b-0184; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 1)
      physical description: folded full sheet, wax seal fragments.; a.l.s.
      Docketed by Alexander.
    - creator: Barclay to J. Alexander. place: London, May 16, 1732; 055-001-b-0187; 1.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 2)
      physical description: folded full sheet, wax seal fragments; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 40cm x 32cm
    - creator: Barclay to J. Alexander. place: London, Sep 26, 1732; 055-001-b-0188; 1.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 3)
      physical description: half sheet, wax seal fragment; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 20cm x 32cm
    - creator: De Wolff, Pedro. place: Amsterdam, Mar 5, 1741; 055-001-b-0189; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 4)
      physical description: fragment of half sheet.; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 17cm x 21cm
      To Mary Alexander. Docketed by J. Alexander.
    - creator: Dongan, Walter. place: s.l., Dec 20, 1745; 055-001-b-0192; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 5)
      dimensions: 39cm x 32cm
      to J. Alexander. Docketed by Alexander.
    - creator: Lumolders, Will. place: s.l., Mar 13, 1747; 055-001-b-0195; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 6)
      physical description: half sheet, multiple repairs; a.l.s.
      to J. Alexander
    - creator: Orem, James. place: London, Mar 27, 1750; 055-001-b-0198; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - creator: Orem, James place: Connington near Stilton in Huntingdon Shire, Sep 4, 1755; 055-001-b-0201; 2.0 pages (Box 3, Folder 8)
      physical description: folded full sheet, repairs, wax fragments; a.l.s.
  - Subseries C: Oversize Materials
    Series I: Subseries C contains oversize material, mainly consisting of deeds and other records of land grants in New York City and State. It is housed in two flat boxes.
    - creator: Beekman, William place: [New Amsterdam], undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      This folder holds a map titled "City of Manhattan or New York" accompanied by a caption describing the life of William Beekman and a translation of the document held in Series I subseries A box 1 folder 31.
      physical description: color print; map; had been mounted and framed with caption and fragment of a sheet (See Series I subseries A Box 1 Folder 31)
      dimensions: 8cm x 10cm
    - creator: Kiefft, Willem. place: New Amsterdam, Mar 22, 1647; 055-001-c-0205; 2.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 2)
      physical description: full sheet, with fragment of second sheet sewn to corner; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 41cm x 32cm
    - creator: Kiefft, Willem. place: New Amsterdam, Apr 2, 1647; 055-001-c-0208; 2.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 3)
      physical description: full sheet, paper and wax seal on recto; a. d.s.
      Land grant of a tract on the east side of Manhattan to Harman Smeeman. On verso: transports to Willem Beekman 1653 and 1656.
    - creator: Stuyvesant, Peter, 1592-1672 place: New Amsterdam, Aug 19, 1664; 055-001-c-0211; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 4)
      physical description: full sheet; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 43cm x 34cm
      Land grant to Jacob Bacher and Isaacq Bedlo.
    - creator: Nicolls, Richard, 1624-1672 place: New York, Feb 13, 1667; 055-001-c-0212; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 5)
      physical description: full sheet with wax seal; a. d.s.
      Confirmation of title for Lucas Dircks
    - creator: Nicolls, Richard, 1624-1672 place: New York, May 22, 1668; 055-001-c-0213; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 6)
      physical description: full sheet with wax seal, substantial repairs; a. d.s.
      Deed of land on Long Island to Charles Ffountaine.
    - creator: Lovelace, Francis. place: New York, Apr 15, 1671; 055-001-c-0214; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 7)
      physical description: parchment, few remnants of broken seal attached; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 43cm x 27cm
      Deed giving land to Jacob Kipp. Recorded by order of Governor Matthias Nicolls. Docketed by Governor Francis Lovelace.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Stephanus, 1642-1700. place: New York, Aug 8, 1699; 055-001-c-0215; 2.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 8)
      physical description: 2 full sheets, deed has 24 wax seals; a. d.s.
      Deed of purchase between Cortlandt and Native Americans for the purchase of land (Mannor Courtlandt). Signed by twenty four Native Americans, John Nanfan, A. De Peyster, Jas. Graham, Rt. Livingston.
    - creator: Van Dam, Rip, ca. 1660-1749. place: s.l., Nov 22, 1737; 055-001-c-0218; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 9)
      physical description: full sheet with remains of wax seal; a. d.s.
      Indenture between Michael D'Graa (Mikal Degree) and John Robinson. Signed in front of Van Dam and H. Demeyer, Jr.
    - creator: De Lancey, James, 1686-1761. place: New York, Jun 1, 1744; 055-001-c-0219; 1.0 pages (Box 4, Folder 10)
      physical description: full sheet with two wax seals; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 39cm x 29cm
      Indenture between De Lancey and Paul Richard.
- Series II: Westchester
  Series II contains documents pertaining to the early history of what is present day Westchester County. It is arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Letters and Documents
    Series II: Subseries A contains a wide range of letters and other documents dating from the late seventeenth century to the middle of the nineteenth century, but the bulk of the material in this subseries dates from the Revolutionary War period. Included within the four legal boxes of this subseries are numerous receipts, orderly and pay books, and correspondence from military officers, including ten documents or letters from George Washington.
    - creator: Walters, Edward., Dec 12, 1684; 055-002-a-0220; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 1)
      physical description: half sheet, badly damaged; d.s.
      Summons to Lewis Morris to appear before the next court of sessions to be held in Westchester.
    - creator: Livingston, Philip, 1716-1778., Apr 13, 17--; 055-002-a-0223; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 2)
      dimensions: 20cm x 31cm
      To Mrs. Nicholas Low regarding a "westchester cheese".
    - creator: Clarke, George. place: New York, Aug 31, 1708; 055-002-a-0224; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 3)
      dimensions: 43cm x 31cm
      Boundary dispute between Eastchester and Westchester.
    - creator: Bridge, Christopher. place: Rye, Apr 13, 1717; 055-002-a-0227; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 4)
      physical description: folded full sheet with wax seal fragment; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 38cm x 31cm
      To Gabriel Bernon.
    - creator: Pell, Thomas. place: Pelham, Mar 20, 1732; 055-002-a-0230; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 5)
      physical description: fragment of half sheet with wax seal; d.s.
      dimensions: 16cm x 21cm
      Pell renounces his right of executorship to the last will and testament of Thomas Parsal.
    - creator: Daniels, William. place: Rye, Dec 17, 1754; 055-002-a-0231; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 6)
      physical description: fragment; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 17cm x 9cm
      Receipt of money from Daniels received by Nehemiah Lyon.
    - creator: Fitch, Thomas, 1700-1774. place: Norwalk, Jan 15, 1757; 055-002-a-0232; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 7)
      physical description: fragment of sheet, partially printed. Mounted in paper frame.; d.s.
      dimensions: 15cm x 14cm
      Resummons Samuel Sely and Samuel Dusenberry of Cortlandt Manor.
    - creator: Marven, Lewis. place: Rye, Dec 13, 1757; 055-002-a-0235; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 8)
      physical description: fragment; d.s.
      dimensions: 19cm x 10cm
      Receipt for money received from Roger Lyon.
    - creator: Livingston, Philip, 1716-1778. place: s.l., Mar 21, 1769; 055-002-a-0236; 4.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 9)
      physical description: folded full sheet with 19 wax seals covered with paper slips; d.s.
      Appointment of arbitrators to settle a dispute over boundaries of East Neck in Mamaroneck. Signed by Livingston, William Alexander, John Jay, and other notables.
    - creator: Seabury, Samuel, 1729-1796. place: Westchester, Oct 5, 1770; 055-002-a-0241; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 10)
      physical description: fragment; Address leaf of letter
      To Dr. Daniel Burton.
    - creator: Rodman, Joseph place: New Rochelle, Jun 1, 1774; 055-002-a-0242; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 11)
      physical description: folded full sheet with wax seal; d.s.
      Contract to repay loan to Samuel Rodman, signed by Joseph Rodman
    - creator: Rodman, Joseph place: New Rochelle, May 2, 1771; 055-002-a-0243; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Indenture between Joseph Rodman and Leonard Lispenard, signed by Rodman
    - creator: Smith, Jaheel place: [Rye], May 14, 1772; 055-002-a-0246; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 12)
      dimensions: 20cm x 7cm
      Receipt of payment received from Roger Lyon
    - creator: Smith, Jaheel place: [Rye], Oct 16, 1772; 055-002-a-0247; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 13)
      dimensions: 20cm x 8cm
      Receipt of payment received from Roger Lyon.
    - creator: Rodman, Joseph place: New Rochelle, Apr 30, 1773; 055-002-a-0248; 4.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 14)
      physical description: full sheet folded twice,multiple repairs; d.s.
      dimensions: 50cm x 39cm
      Deed of 'Neck of Land' to Leonard Lispenard
    - creator: Lyon, Roger. place: Rye, Sep 20, 1773; 055-002-a-0253; 1.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 15)
      dimensions: 19cm x 8cm
      Receipt for purchase of rum by Lyon.
    - creator: Strong, Nehemiah, 1729-1807 place: Hartford, Jun 3, 1774; 055-002-a-0254; 2.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 16)
      dimensions: 20cm x 22cm
      Expense account for an expedition to Byram's River. Signed by Samuel H. Parsons and Roger Sherman.
    - creator: Manuscript Account Book place: White Plains, Jul 1776; 055-002-a-0266; 20.0 pages (Box 5, Folder 17)
      physical description: multiple folded sheets sewn together; d.s.
      dimensions: 11cm x 19cm
      Account book, likely for Bradley's Battalion of Connecticut
    - creator: Waterman, Asa. place: Saw Pitts, Nov 1, 1776; 055-002-a-0356 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 10cm
      Receipt for one barrel flour
    - creator: Stiles, Reuben. place: North Castle, Nov 13, 1776; 055-002-a-0374 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 17cm x 6cm
      Receipt for six barrels of flour
    - creator: Huntington, Joshua place: North Castle, Nov 15, 1776; 055-002-a-0299 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 11cm
      Receipt for 5,650 dollars
    - creator: Tracy, Jared. place: Saw Pitts, Nov 21, 1776; 055-002-a-0296 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 9cm
      Receipt for 150 pounds lawful money
    - creator: Smith, Jonathan. place: Saw Pitts, Nov 25, 1776; 055-002-a-0317 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 11cm
      Receipt for cash, also signed by Josiah Scovil
    - creator: Smith, Robert place: Saw Pitts, Nov 28, 1776; 055-002-a-0383 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for six shillings and six pence for oysters
    - creator: Richardson, James place: Congressbridge, Oct 1, 1776; 055-002-a-0302 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for barrels of flour distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Sands, Joshua place: Congressbridge, Oct 11, 1776; 055-002-a-0326 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for eight barrels of flour distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Sands, Joshua place: Congressbridge, Oct 13, 1776; 055-002-a-0389 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 17cm
      Receipt for thirty five barrels of flour distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Jameson, John place: Saw Pitts, Oct 14, 1776; 055-002-a-0359 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 16cm
      Receipt for pails and canteens, also signed by James Earl
    - creator: Bate, James place: Kingsbridge, Oct 15, 1776; 055-002-a-0308 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 20cm
      Receipt for barrels of pork and rum distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Phillips, Samuel place: Congressbridge, Oct 16, 1776; 055-002-a-0398 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for two hogsheads of rum
    - creator: Waterman, Asa place: [Rye], Oct 16, 1776; 055-002-a-0386 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for ten barrels of flour
    - creator: Squire, John place: East Chester, Oct 17, 1776; 055-002-a-0287 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 16cm x 8cm
      Receipt for eight barrels of pork
    - creator: Squire, John. place: East Chester, Oct 17, 1776; 055-002-a-0329 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 17cm x 13cm
      Receipt
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 18, 1776; 055-002-a-0347 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 6cm
      Receipt for five casks pork, no transcription
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 18, 1776; 055-002-a-0380 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for six forty gallon cask pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: s.l., Oct 18, 1776; 055-002-a-0401 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for two hogsheads rum
    - creator: Horton, Gilb place: Mamaroneck, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0392 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 9cm
      Receipt for twenty one barrels pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0404 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 8cm
      Receipt for eight barrels of pork and one barrel of flour
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0407 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for nine barrels of pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0335 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for six barrels of pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0338 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for eight barrels pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0350 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for seven barrels pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0360 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 19, 1776; 055-002-a-0377 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for two hogsheads rum and five tents
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 21, 1776; 055-002-a-0371 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for nine half-barrels pork
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 21, 1776; 055-002-a-0353 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for seven half-barrels pork
    - creator: Tracy, Jared. place: Saw Pitts, Oct 21, 1776; 055-002-a-0341 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for fifty eight pounds lawfull money
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 22, 1776; 055-002-a-0323 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for eight barrels flour
    - creator: Tracy, Frederick. place: White Plains, Oct 22, 1776; 055-002-a-0320 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - creator: Wadsworth, Jeremiah place: Saw Pitts, Oct 27, 1776; 055-002-a-0314 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 21cm x 32cm
      Receipt for buckets, canteens, onions and corn
    - creator: Squire, John place: East Chester, Oct 3, 1776; 055-002-a-0362 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 16cm x 11cm
      Receipt for pork and flour
    - creator: Richardson, James place: Congressbridge, Oct 5, 1776; 055-002-a-0395 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for twenty seven barrels of flour distributed from magazine
    - creator: Bate, James place: Kingsbridge, Oct 8, 1776; 055-002-a-0332 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 6cm
    - creator: Sands, Joshua place: Kingsbridge, Sep 20, 1776; 055-002-a-0344 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 20cm x 23cm
      Receipt for barrels of pork and flour distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Trumbull, Jonathan, 1710-1785 place: Lebanon, Sep 21, 1776; 055-002-a-0260 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for 500 pounds lawfull money
    - creator: Richardson, James place: Kingsbridge, Sep 22, 1776; 055-002-a-0305 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - creator: Sands, Joshua place: Kingsbridge, Sep 23, 1776; 055-002-a-0344 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for five barrels of flour
    - creator: Trumbull, Joseph, 1737-1778 place: West Chester, Sep 24, 1776; 055-002-a-0257 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Order to supply "nesesary Provision"